<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
  <Tweets>
    <Tweet>Billy Graham was a humble servant who prayed for so many - and who, with wisdom and grace, gave hope and guidance t… https://t.co/V8WtgIRPEB</Tweet>
    <Tweet>We are grieving with Parkland. But we are not powerless. Caring for our kids is our first job. And until we can hon… https://t.co/LWGSkzRapH</Tweet>
    <Tweet>Happy Valentine’s Day, @MichelleObama. You make every day and every place better. https://t.co/aWvyytR7Mm</Tweet>
    <Tweet>RT @MichelleObama: Happy #ValentinesDay to my one and only, @BarackObama. To celebrate the occasion, I’m dedicating a little Valentine’s Da…</Tweet>
    <Tweet>Dr. King was 26 when the Montgomery bus boycott began. He started small, rallying others who believed their efforts… https://t.co/N0zwBg7gTi</Tweet>
    <Tweet>All across America people chose to get involved, get engaged and stand up. Each of us can make a difference, and al… https://t.co/zxpKVnNeHZ</Tweet>
    <Tweet>Ten-year-old Jahkil Jackson is on a mission to help homeless people in Chicago. He created kits full of socks, toil… https://t.co/7mNk6dmnyC</Tweet>
    <Tweet>Chris Long gave his paychecks from the first six games of the NFL season to fund scholarships in Charlottesville, V… https://t.co/KxUk5Wle6h</Tweet>
    <Tweet>Kat Creech, a wedding planner in Houston, turned a postponed wedding into a volunteer opportunity for Hurricane Har… https://t.co/MCXiSuAVJN</Tweet>
    <Tweet>As we count down to the new year, we get to reflect and prepare for what’s ahead. For all the bad news that seemed… https://t.co/WaUHkVww2g</Tweet>
    <Tweet>RT @MBK_Alliance: I am my Brother’s Keeper. 
Watch our new PSA with @BarackObama, @StephenCurry30 &amp;amp; @chancetherapper, then take action to s…</Tweet>
    <Tweet>On behalf of the Obama family, Merry Christmas! We wish you joy and peace this holiday season. https://t.co/CNFUZrhrBj</Tweet>
    <Tweet>There's no better time than the holiday season to reach out and give back to our communities. Great to hear from yo… https://t.co/gp5dCy9oN2</Tweet>
    <Tweet>Happy Hanukkah, everybody, from the Obama family to yours. Chag Sameach!</Tweet>
    <Tweet>Just got off a call to thank folks who are working hard to help more Americans across the country sign up for healt… https://t.co/A9QvCySWJ8</Tweet>
    <Tweet>RT @ObamaFoundation: Watch: We hosted a Town Hall in New Delhi with @BarackObama and young leaders about how to drive change and make an im…</Tweet>
    <Tweet>Michelle and I are delighted to congratulate Prince Harry and Meghan Markle on their engagement. We wish you a life… https://t.co/KC9nmjZPuX</Tweet>
    <Tweet>From the Obama family to yours, we wish you a Happy Thanksgiving full of joy and gratitude. https://t.co/xAvSQwjQkz</Tweet>
    <Tweet>ME:  Joe, about halfway through the speech, I’m gonna wish you a happy birth--
BIDEN:  IT’S MY BIRTHDAY!
ME:  Joe.… https://t.co/5qLUsDoaMi</Tweet>
    <Tweet>RT @ObamaFoundation: Today, we honor those who have honored our country with its highest form of service. https://t.co/IbJNCwIofL https://t…</Tweet>
 <Tweets>